[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
Damn it.
Get in the car!
"The Last Oath"
(Episode 10: Mobility & Feul)
Stop the car.
Listen, friend.
This blade doesn't discriminate.
One bump in the road,
and we're all done for.
If I wanted to hurt you,
I wouldn't have picked you up back there.
Green Island Airport isn't far ahead.
Once we get there, you
can have the car back.
And I'll go my own way.
Deal?
It's the end of the world,
why are you going to an airport?
Is your camp set up there?
No.
I'm looking for my younger brother.
When I lost contact with him,
he was at Green Island Airport.
Terminal 2.
It's been so long.
You think he's still holding out for you?
I have to at least try.
In this apocalyptic world,
if you don't have hope,
what else keeps you going?
We're almost out of gas.
There should be fuel at the airport.
Let's go inside and look.
We're already at the airport.
Why are you still following us?
I didn't expect there to
be so many of them inside.
If I go alone,
I probably won't make it far.
It's safer to stick with you guys.
Looking like that,
and you dared to come out
alone to find your brother?
Well, I ran into you guys, didn't I?
Don't worry, I won't drag you down.
Nothing.
Let's check the planes.
It won't open.
It's getting dark.
Searching like this is too inefficient.
And it's not safe.
Let's find a place to rest for the night.
Who found the instant noodles?
I did.
Found them over there.
Slightly expired,
but they should still be edible.
I checked the plastic wrap.
They're all intact.
You guys are pretty cautious.
We've been through thick
and thin together now.
I don't have any bad
intentions toward you.
Just don't try to stab
me in the back either.
I'll go boil some water.
Speaking of which,
we haven't even introduced ourselves.
We don't even know what to call each other.
There's no need for that.
Come on, let's be friends.
We might run into each other again.
I'm He Yao.
He as in congratulate,
Yao with three earth radicals.
I heard you call him A-Leh.
What about you?
Lin Zai.
Lin with two wood radicals,
Zai as in present.
You look pretty young.
Were you still in school
before the apocalypse?
I was a senior in college.
Which school?
Anjing.
Then we're alumni!
You're my junior.
I just remember
our school cafeteria food was awful.
I used to go to that street
stall outside the west gate.
Do you remember Lao Er's Fried Rice?
Their stir-fried shrimp
over rice was amazing.
It's been years since I graduated,
and I still crave it.
It was good, sure,
but the line was a nightmare.
Every time we went, it
was at least a half-hour wait.
And in the winter,
our faces would freeze and crack.
Senior,
what was your major?
Chemistry.
Are you that He Yao who won
the gold medal from the event
held at MIT for the International
Genetics Competition?
That was so many years ago.
Back then, the two giants of
the pharmaceutical industry,
Herin and Casia, were fighting over you.
Where did you end up?
Both offered great terms,
but my talks with Herin didn't go well.
I always felt like
they treated people
like mere tools.
Are you okay?
Anyway, the apocalypse happened,
so it's all the same now.
Well,
I'm done eating.
Get some sleep.
We still have to look for gas tomorrow.
It's okay.
Take your time.
Is one bowl enough?
Don't be shy.
My brother used to be like this too.
The first time I saw you,
you reminded me of him.
Actually, I have an older brother too.
What a coincidence.
So,
is he doing okay now?
I'm going to the restroom.
Don't overstep your bounds.
I think you're just being overly paranoid.
Not everyone harbors bad intentions.
Don't judge others by your own standards.
Lin Zai and I
just hit it off, that's all.
He and my brother
are really alike.
Lin Zai is not your brother.
Stop projecting.
Just a reminder,
people who are too controlling
aren't very likable.
Want a smoke?
No, I don't.
What?
You don't either?
I didn't use to smoke either.
But it's the apocalypse now.
Gotta find something to take the edge off.
Try it.
It's no big deal.
Don't touch things you shouldn't.
Looks like they haven't gone far.
We need to find him as soon as possible
and take him back for experiments.